http://www.irishmoiledcattlesociety.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Irish Moiled Cattle Society Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how the Irish Moiled Cattle Society (‘us’, ‘we’) uses and protects any information that you give us when you apply for membership, use our website and/or online herd book.The Irish Moiled Cattle Society is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and we may exercise legitimate interests if we feel appropriate. This privacy statement describes the online information practices which we the Irish Moiled Cattle Society employ in relating to the information which you, our members/customers (‘you’, ‘your’) provide when applying for or using:  membership (our membership database)  www.irishmoiledcattlesociety.com (website)  www.grassroots.co.uk/imoiled (our online herd book)By accessing and using these services you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Statement.Irish Moiled Cattle Society may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25th May 2018. If you do not agree with our policy we would suggest you do not use our services.  What we collectWe may collect the following information:namecontact information including email addressdemographic information such as postcodeWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping.  We may use the information to improve services.  We may periodically send update/information emails about new/changes in services and fees, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.   From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for research purposes. We may contact you by email or phone. We may use the information to customise the website and online herd book according to your interests.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  How we use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  We may use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:You need to notify us in writingIf you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for membership purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at .We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Breed SecretaryShamrock Vale42 Belfast RoadGlenavyCrumlinCo AntrimBT29 4HR
SitemapThe Moilie StoryBuy BeefHomepageThe SocietyThe BreedIrish Moilie BeefIrish Moilie Beef SchemeNews and EventsContact UsStock For SaleBreeders ResourcesPrize Draw Online EntryGDPR Opt-inTerms and Conditions – Grand Draw 2020ClassificationNew MembersSemen For SaleBreed HistorySociety RulesMembershipMerchandisePrivacy PolicyHerd Book LoginMembership PaymentAGMMoiled TimesCartCheckoutMy account
Search
Stock for Sale
Irish Moilie Beef
Contact Us
Facebook
Instagram
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
